[{"answer": "Well, you know, I can hope it will end.", "docId": "110909pmt", "aSentId": 37, "question": "Do you ever see a time when it will end in your lifetime?", "qSentId": 36}, {"answer": "Well, Cantor Fitzgerald September 10th, 2001 was a winning organization.", "docId": "110909pmt", "aSentId": 46, "question": "And how do you think you've changed sin what happened in the next day?", "qSentId": 45}, {"answer": "Well, I took a picture with my son, you know, sort of the classic wet behind the ears, the backpack picture about 8:45, I have the picture.", "docId": "110909pmt", "aSentId": 69, "question": "What was the precise moment that you heard there was something going down at the tower?", "qSentId": 68}, {"answer": "Yes, it's impossible for it to have happened.", "docId": "110909pmt", "aSentId": 87, "question": "This must have been the absolute, ultimate nightmare for you, wasn't it?", "qSentId": 86}, {"answer": "Well, you know, so I was in my car.", "docId": "110909pmt", "aSentId": 102, "question": "As you looked up at the towers, what was the moment for you that you certainly feared that there was going to be no way out for your friends and employees?", "qSentId": 101}, {"answer": "I'm thinking that -- that I'm done.", "docId": "110909pmt", "aSentId": 153, "question": "What are you thinking in that moment?", "qSentId": 152}, {"answer": "My sister, she was with me at school.", "docId": "110909pmt", "aSentId": 176, "question": "I think -- didn't she take a call before the tower came down from your brother in the tower, is that right?", "qSentId": 175}, {"answer": "Well, my wife told me that one of my senior partners was alive and he lived in Greenwich Village, which I thought, all right, I could just walk there.", "docId": "110909pmt", "aSentId": 206, "question": "What was the moment for you when you reassessed that, when you got a feeling, it's not done, I can turn this in to a positive?", "qSentId": 205}, {"answer": "Well, so we decided -- we had a call at 11:00 at night.", "docId": "110909pmt", "aSentId": 255, "question": "Way, way more than they would ever have expected?", "qSentId": 254}, {"answer": "Until I was able to send them money, and by the way, you sent them money on October 22nd.", "docId": "110909pmt", "aSentId": 294, "question": "An enemy figure until the money began to come and they could see that you were going to be good to your promise?", "qSentId": 293}, {"answer": "I was sitting at home, just watching television with my family.", "docId": "110909pmt", "aSentId": 320, "question": "Howard, where were you when you heard that Navy SEALS had shot and killed Osama bin Laden?", "qSentId": 319}, {"answer": "Well, you saw on television, there was these crowds at the White House chanting USA, USA.", "docId": "110909pmt", "aSentId": 332, "question": "Did you feel any kind of closure?", "qSentId": 331}, {"answer": "Well, you know, the National September 11 Museum is opening that morning.", "docId": "110909pmt", "aSentId": 348, "question": "How do you intend to commemorate the day?", "qSentId": 347}, {"answer": "You know, I was orphaned when I was young.", "docId": "110909pmt", "aSentId": 399, "question": "How do you think you've changed as a human being through what's happened?", "qSentId": 398}, {"answer": "I think people in Washington spend too much time in Washington.", "docId": "110909pmt", "aSentId": 445, "question": "How can America get itself back on its feet?", "qSentId": 444}, {"answer": "ANNING: I reached the lobby.", "docId": "110909pmt", "aSentId": 506, "question": "What happen?", "qSentId": 505}, {"answer": "It was a bond trader at another firm.", "docId": "110909pmt", "aSentId": 521, "question": "You know who it is, don't you?", "qSentId": 520}, {"answer": "I think it was a combination of how I was raised.", "docId": "110909pmt", "aSentId": 531, "question": "How have you found the courage and the strength to battle through?", "qSentId": 530}, {"answer": "He was the driving force that day in my decision to live.", "docId": "110909pmt", "aSentId": 547, "question": "How important was it for you to have not just your husband, but also that little baby, who you had to bring up as a mother, despite what you were going through?", "qSentId": 546}, {"answer": "I will be, as I always am, with my Cantor Fitzgerald family.", "docId": "110909pmt", "aSentId": 557, "question": "Where will you be, Lauren, on Sunday when the anniversary takes place?", "qSentId": 556}, {"answer": "I felt this sense that it was good we got the titular head, as it was, of al Qaeda.", "docId": "110909pmt", "aSentId": 562, "question": "Did you feel any sense of closure when Osama bin Laden was killed?", "qSentId": 561}]